<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Delegate Pattern</title>
    <link>https://delegatepattern.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Delegate Pattern</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 15:14:26 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://delegatepattern.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Finally I Cracked the Code</title>
      <link>https://delegatepattern.com/posts/finally-i-cracked-the-code/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 15:14:26 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://delegatepattern.com/posts/finally-i-cracked-the-code/</guid>
      <description>Finally I wrote in Russian right
Well, I finally did it.

This is my greatest accomplishment of 2016

But I think wins come in all sizes — big wins and small.
I feel good about my writing. It took me over a year to get good. I don’t really care how many people made fun of me for my writing (trust me, I know how horrible they look).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://delegatepattern.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2016 07:47:31 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://delegatepattern.com/about/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;ll help your business build powerful software, unstoppable conversion, and unbeatable success.&amp;rdquo; Hi, my name is Kasem. Senior software consultant with over 15 years of experience.
I help specialized, successful software and SaaS companies create high-quality mobile apps with expertise-driven software consulting.

2016 - Producing new educational material.

Have questions? send me a private message.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code Encapsulation in iOS With Swift</title>
      <link>https://delegatepattern.com/posts/code-encapsulation-in-ios-with-swift/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2016 07:17:21 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://delegatepattern.com/posts/code-encapsulation-in-ios-with-swift/</guid>
      <description>One of the places where most iOS developers make object oriented design mistakes is putting all UI code inside view controllers.
This will lead to an unmanageable and massive view controller. Thus, this clearly violates the MVC pattern guideline.
Let’s be real. You found your way here because you have an interest to know how to make your view controller cleaner and separate concerns and responsibilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An UNBEATABLE Guarantee</title>
      <link>https://delegatepattern.com/unbeatable-guarantee/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://delegatepattern.com/unbeatable-guarantee/</guid>
      <description>I start every business relationship with my 7-Day Unbeatable 100% Money-Back Guarantee.
Try my software consulting service for a full 7-days, 100% risk-free. If you don&amp;rsquo;t LOVE it, I insist that you get 100% of your money back. I&amp;rsquo;ll even eat the credit-card processing fees.
In short: You will get your money back and keep all the work completed as my gift to you.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
